addmembers.com 2017-01-10

# Privacy Policy —

We are RainMaker MA Software and our affiliated companies worldwide are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) you share with us.

RainMaker MA Software has established this Online Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your Personal Information.

Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. In general, you can visit RainMaker MA Software’ Web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself.

RainMaker MA Software strives to comply with all applicable laws around the globe that are designed to protect your privacy. Although legal requirements may vary from country to country, RainMaker MA Software intends to adhere to the principles set forth in this Online Privacy Policy even if, in connection with the above, we transfer your Personal Information from your country to countries that may not require an “adequate” level of protection for your Personal Information. In other words, our goal is to provide protection for your Personal Information no matter where that Personal Information is collected, transferred, or retained.

Some of our Web pages utilize “cookies” and other tracking technologies. A “cookie” is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about Web site activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Web user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them.

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of the Web site as well as break the tracking to affiliate commissions.

Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; click-stream patterns; and dates and times that our site is accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our Web site and your Web experience. We may also analyze information that does not contain Personal Information for trends and statistics.

To protect your privacy, we have adopted the following principles:

Notice

Choice

Security

Access/Accuracy

Where RainMaker MA Software collects Personal Information on the web, we intend to post a purpose statement that explains why Personal Information will be collected and whether we plan to share such Personal Information outside of RainMaker MA Software or those working on RainMaker MA Software’ behalf. RainMaker MA Software does not intend to transfer Personal Information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on RainMaker MA Software behalf unless such transfer is legally required.

You may choose whether or not to provide Personal Information to RainMaker MA Software. The notice we intend to provide where RainMaker MA Software collects Personal Information on the Web should help you to make this choice. If you choose not to provide the Personal Information we request, you can still visit most of RainMaker MA Software Web sites, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers, and services that involve our interaction with you.

If you chose to have a relationship with RainMaker MA Software, such as a contractual or other business relationship or partnership, we will naturally continue to contact you in connection with that business relationship.

Wherever your Personal Information may be held within RainMaker MA Software or on its behalf, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the Personal Information that you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure.

To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, RainMaker MA Software wishes to maintain accurate Personal Information. Where we collect Personal Information from you on the Web, our goal is to provide a means of contacting RainMaker MA Software should you need to update or correct that Information. If for any reason those means are unavailable or inaccessible, you may send updates and corrections about your Personal Information to privacy@StrategicProfits.com and we will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes in your Personal Information that we hold as soon as practicable.

Third parties provide certain services available on RainMaker MA Software.com on RainMaker MA Software behalf. RainMaker MA Software may provide information, including Personal Information, which RainMaker MA Software collects on the Web to third-party service providers to help us deliver programs, products, information, and services. Service providers are also an important means by which RainMaker MA Software maintains its Web site and mailing lists. RainMaker MA Software will take reasonable steps to ensure that these third-party service providers are obligated to protect Personal Information on RainMaker MA Software’ behalf.

RainMaker MA Software does not intend to transfer Personal Information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on RainMaker MA Software behalf unless such transfer is legally required. Similarly, it is against RainMaker MA Software’ policy to sell Personal Information collected online without consent.

RainMaker MA Software can only refund transactions within 60 days from the date of purchase.

RainMaker MA Software.com is not structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age although we currently do not take steps to verify the user to that extent.

We are committed to privacy are actively involved in and support current industry initiatives to preserve individual privacy rights on the Internet. Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and RainMaker MA Software Web sites are constantly evolving to meet these demands.

If you have any comments or questions regarding our Online Privacy Policy, please contact us at info@addmembers.com

While we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as possible.

By using this Web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy, Terms and Conditions of Use, and to RainMaker MA Software processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above as well as those explained where RainMaker MA Software collects Personal Information on the Web. Should the Online Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our web site for a reasonable period of time.
